你知道我打一开始就喜欢你
You knew I liked you right from the start
如果你允许我就把心给你
You knew that if you'd let me I'd give you my heart
但你从未给我过这样的机会
But you never gave me the time of day
甚至是一点迹象
never showed any sign
除了我每次都提到你
Instead every time I talked to you
那最美的外形
you laid out your favorite line
你说啊亲爱的
You said honey
我得出去一趟见见人
I got places to go and people to see
我尽我所能吸引你的注意力
I tried to get your attention in any way that I could
甚至在空中翻转 但对我并没什么好处
I did flips in the air, but it did me no good
唯一好像能对你起作用的
The only thing that seemed to work on you
就是我最后做的决定
was when I finally made up my mind
艰难地作出决定
To never lay my eyes on you
为了再也不关注你
and play the hard to get kind
所以我说啊亲爱的
So I said baby
我也一样得出去一趟见见人
I too got places to go and people to see
哦 哦 亲爱的
Oh oh baby
我也一样得出去一趟见见人
I too got places to go and people to see
你真的不知道何时该放下
Boy you really don't know when to quit
（不知道何时该放下）
(Don't know when to quit)
告诉我如何才能让你明白
Tell me how can I help you take a hint
（让你明白）
(Take a hint)
这游戏多年前就结束了
This game was over ages ago
我赢了 你输了
I won, you lost
没错我内心还是拒绝的
and yes my answer is still no
没关系 亲爱的
That's right honey
我也一样得出去一趟见见人
I got places to go and people to see
我是真的爱你
I love you truly
但我现在就出门
But I'm walking out the door now
别打扰我
Don't bother me
我现在就出门
I'm walking out the door now
好好看看我
Take a good look at me
我现在就出门
I'm walking out the door now
别跟着我
Don't follow me